民粹主义政客 曼弗雷德·费斯特
'The populist politician Manfred Fest
在慕尼黑遇刺
'was struck by a sniper in Munich.
费斯特当时正要去圣伊丽莎白医院看望儿子 埃利亚斯·费斯特
'Fest was visiting his son, Elias Fest at the Saint Elizabeth hospital.'
埃利亚斯·费斯特接手管理费斯特出版集团
人们纷纷猜测这两起事件的关联
'This has sparked speculation concerning a connection between these incidents.'
狙击手有一把能让他在这个距离射击的枪
'When a sniper finds a rifle that allows him to make a shot at that distance,
这把枪可太牛了
that rifle is a keeper.'
有个造枪的人这些年一直尝试这么做
There's a gun maker who's been trying to do this.
他叫诺曼·斯托克
His name is Norman Stoke.
我在贝尔法斯特有个线人 代号麻雀
'I have an asset in Belfast. Codename Sparrow.'
拉里要是知道我和你说话 会杀了我
If Larry knew who I was talking to, he'd kill me.
她有个女儿 叫艾玛
'She has a daughter, Emma.'
-我一定能找到他  -别让我失望
- 'I know I can find him.' - Don't let me down.
非常欣赏你的工作 我们有一个项目 相信你会感兴趣 报酬极为丰厚
目标是谁
Who's the target?
乌勒·达格·查尔斯
Ulle Dag Charles.
资流是革命性技术
River is a revolutionary technology.
你能办到吗
Can you get to him?
价格会很高
It'll cost.
预计什么时候？
24小时查询账户
未收到付款
慕尼黑的375万欧元仍未支付
去你
妈的
你让我抓的学生出了大问题
We've got a serious problem with your student.
她没心跳了
She's arrested.
豺狼的日子
第一季 第二集
在德国 曼弗雷德·费斯特的支持者们
'In Germany, supporters of Manfred Fest
伦敦  英国
继续要求推迟即将进行的联邦选举
'continue to call for the upcoming federal elections to be postponed.
他的政治对手否认他们拒绝延期
'His political opponents deny that their resistance to this
是对费斯特及其家人的不尊重
'...is a mark of disrespect to Fest and his family.
麻雀
曼弗雷德·费斯特的儿子 埃利亚斯也...
'Manfred Fest's son, Elias was also...'
谁是麻雀
Who's Sparrow?
给我 给我 给我
Gimme, Gimme, Gimme. Gimme, Gimme, Gimme, Gimme, Gimme.
-艾莉森 等我一下  -早上好
- Alison, just give me a moment. - Morning.
你就是个该死的婊子
'You're a fucking bitch, you know that?'
艾莉森 发生什么了
Alison, what's going on?
别跟我说这是巧合
'Don't tell me this is a coincidence.'
你突然出现 之后艾玛就被逮捕了
You suddenly turning up out the blue and next thing Emma's arrested.
他们不让我跟她讲话
'They're not letting me speak to her.
你这么做肯定是为了报复我
'And I know you're doing this to get at me.'
我跟这件事没关系
I've got nothing to do with it.
你是个骗子
'You're a liar.'
你为什么要给我打电话 艾莉森
Why are you calling me, Alison?
你他妈非常清楚我为什么要打给你
'You know fucking fine rightly why I'm calling.'
你肯定能把她弄出来
I know you can get her out.
你之前把我弄出来了
You got me out.
对 那时你有对我价值
Yeah, you had something to offer back then.
把诺曼的手机号码给我 其余的事交给我处理
Just get me Norman's phone number, and I'll do the rest.
我今天就要拿到
'And I want it today.'
初步报告显示 艾玛先前患有心脏病
The preliminary report says Emma had a preexisting heart condition.
她死在哪都是可能的
She could've died anywhere.
但她死在了拘留室 而且是你把她关进去的
But she died in a police cell, and you put her there.
杀了曼弗雷德·费斯特的人
The man who killed Manfred Fest
会再次动手杀人 除非我们提前阻止他
will kill again, unless we stop him.
所以这算连带伤害吗
So, collateral damage?
我不会这么说
I wouldn't put it that way.
那你觉得应该算什么
What way would you put it?
一个不该死 却死了的女孩
A girl died who shouldn't have died.
这位是卡弗先生 他负责为我们善后
This is Mr Carver. He cleans up messes for us.
幸运的是他专程来为你善后
And you're very lucky he's here to clean up yours.
那女孩被警方拘留了
The girl was in police custody.
意味着警方负有法律责任
That makes the police legally responsible,
但我要万无一失的确保
but it is my job to make certain,
军情六处不能与这件事有任何关联
one hundred percent, that MI6 can't be connected in any way.
还有谁知道你那天在警局
So, who knows you were at the police station?
全部事情都是由吉莱斯皮办的
Everything went through Gillespie.
-那个警察  -对
- The copper? - Yeah.
他甚至是唯一知道我名字的人
He's the only one who even knows my name.
我要跟吉莱斯皮谈谈
I'll have a word with Gillespie,
确保没有别人能认出她
make sure no one else can identify her.
-还有别人吗  -没了
- Anyone else? - No.
-你确定吗  -对
- You're sure? - Yes.
希望吉莱斯皮值得信任
Let's hope Gillespie can be trusted.
我们得马上终止这项行动
We need to close this operation down, now.
我今早和麻雀刚通过话 她已经上钩了
I spoke to Sparrow this morning. She's on the hook.
你跟她说她女儿已经死了吗
Did you tell her that her daughter's dead?!
没有
I did not.
你还想让情况变得更糟吗
You're in a hole and you want to keep digging?
一位重要的政治人物被暗杀了
A major political figure has been assassinated,
而且杀手所用的枪极有可能是英国人造的
and there's a strong probability that the gun was made by a British gunmaker,
我有这个人的线索
and I have a lead on him.
你想要撒手不管吗
Are you saying we should just walk away?
这可能会白费力气 对部门声誉没什么好处
This is a wild goose chase, and it's not helping our department's reputation.
我们应该把这件事交给中欧部门处理
We should offload this to the Central Europe desk.
我向德国方面保证过我们会帮忙
I promised the Germans we'd help.
发生在艾玛身上的事 虽然很不幸
Emma's... is unfortunate,
但这是不得不采取的手段
but it's ends and means.
就目前来看 目的达成了
And in this instance, ends trump.
不能让艾莉森知道艾玛已经死了
Alison cannot find out about Emma.
一旦她知道真相 我就会失去她的信任
Once that news breaks, I've lost her.
我能为你争取一些时间
I can buy you some time.
能争取多久
How long?
大概24小时
Twenty-four hours maybe.
你最好开始行动吧
You'd better get to work.
快接
Come on.
怎么了
'Yes?'
我有些好消息要讲
I've got some good news.
我跟上级谈过了 我能放艾玛出来
'I've talked to my bosses, and I can get Emma out.
-好消息 对吗  -对
- Great, right?' - Yes.
但你要把诺曼的手机号码给我 我今天就要拿到
But I need you to get me Norman's phone number, and I need it today.
别担心 艾玛很快就能回家
Don't worry, Emma'll be home soon.
乌勒·达格·查尔斯 (乌达查)
他在瑞典哥德堡长大 后前往美国 就读于普林斯顿大学并中途退学 他加入了美国国籍
真名为苏莱曼·达格·金 1972年出生于利比亚的的黎波里 母亲是巴勒斯坦人 父亲是爱沙尼亚人
他是商业巨头 科技企业家 产品架构师和富有远见的投资者
他是世界上最富有的人之一 他在24岁时创立了达格豪斯公司 积累了大量财富 该公司致力于
开发新技术 为全球提供金融服务 他对个人生活守口如瓶 极为低调 虽然他的婚姻状况未知 但...
他是商业巨头 科技企业家 产品架构师和富有远见的投资者
最新项目
资流
他的新项目资流，据传是为了开启金融透明和全球经济正义
的新时代。批评者说这将使世界陷入难以想象的混乱
欢迎！
开曼大都会银行
登录
安全登录
用户名：阿拉斯泰尔 瑟斯克
重置
登录
安全聊天
14天前有375万欧元被存入我的账户，请求确认资金来源
早啊 亲爱的
早上好
Morning.
我能看出
I can see when you are...
你心事重重
每当你专注于工作 就会像这样出神
When you go to that place you go when you are thinking about work.
我在这儿呢
I'm here.
只有一部分在
Only half.
告诉另一部分快回来
Tell the other half to come.
我很想他
I miss him.
有些同我合作的人
There's someone I've been working with, has, um...
他们对合约有些误解
Well, they've misunderstood their obligations to me.
是钱的问题吗
Is it money?
对
Yeah.
数目很大吗
A lot?
对
Yeah.
太可恶了
你准备怎么做
What are you gonna do?
这不只是钱的问题
It's not just the money.
要是消息传出去 其他人得知
It's that if it were to get out that someone had...
有人没向我付钱 会有损我的声誉
...got away without paying me, it, it hurts the brand.
这才是最严重的
Which is a problem.
我知道
I know.
要是他占了你的便宜
And if he steals from you...
他就是占你家人的便宜
...he steals from your family,
也就是占我和卡利托斯的便宜
which is me and Carlito.
告诉我他住在哪 我会去拿他欠的钱
So you tell me where he lives, and I get the money he owes.
怎么
What?
-我会去拿 相信我  -好 我毫不怀疑
- I will do it, trust me. - Yeah, I don't fucking doubt it.
我不会质疑你
I do not doubt that.
不过别担心 我会处理好
But don't worry, I'll sort it.
还有笔交易仍在酝酿之中
There's another deal brewing.
是笔大单吗
Is it big?
等做完这单 我就可以有更多时间陪你们了
Well, it would mean that I could spend a lot more time with you two.
雇佣你的人认为
The people you work for think that,
他们付你很多钱 你就要任由他们差遣
because they pay you a lot of money, they own your soul.
这是什么表情
What is that look?
什么
What?
-有时候你看我的时候  -怎么
- Sometimes you look at me and... - What?
我不知道
I don't know.
别呀 什么意思 看我的时候怎么了
No, what do you mean? Sometimes you look at me?
-你想说什么  -我不知道
- And... what do you mean? - I don't know.
看我的时候怎么了
Sometimes you look at me and what?
你看到什么了
What do you see?
-我看到一个混蛋  -去你的
- I see a motherfucker. - Fuck you.
纽约  美国
今早我刮胡子的时候
I was shaving this morning,
突然意识到
and it hit me.
经济学家们都搞错了
The economists are wrong.
我们轻易就能使世界人口数目减半
We could easily lose half the world's population
同时还不会有任何负面影响
and there'd be no downside.
当然 要减少应该消失的人
Would have to be the right half, of course.
现在问题在于 杀死曼弗雷德·费斯特的那个人是否值得我们信任
Now, the question is, can we trust the man who killed Manfred Fest?
利奥诺拉让我给你找顶尖杀手 我就是依照这个标准选的
Leonora asked me to find you the best,. That's what I've done.
他显然可以胜任
He's clearly capable,
但一亿美元可是一笔巨款
but a hundred mil is a hell of a lot of money to spend.
他完成任务后我们才需要付钱
Well, we only pay if he delivers.
但要是他完成了 也算是物有所值
And if he delivers, it'll be worth it.
谢谢 见到你很高兴 感谢你的到来
Thank you. Good to see you. Thanks for coming in.
乌勒·达格·查尔斯 你将要发布一款软件 资流
Ulle Dag Charles, you're about to launch a product, River,
你承诺这将为全球带来经济正义
which you're promising will deliver global economic justice.
为什么你这么有钱的人会对经济正义感兴趣
Why is the richest man on the planet so interested in economic justice?
我们大家都应该对经济正义感兴趣
Well, we should all be interested in economic justice.
就这么简单 不是吗
It's a simple as that. Right?
你的父母是左派激进分子
Your parents were leftist radicals.
有人会说你这么做是为了取悦父母
Some would say you're trying to please mom and dad.
哦 拜托
Oh, come on.
金钱源源不断流入富豪的口袋
Look, money runs like water into the pockets of the superrich
并且不再外流
and stays there.
但这些钱应该用于支持未来社会的发展
Instead it should run into reservoirs for future generations.
而全面财务透明
And the only way to do that
就是实现该目标的唯一途径
is total financial transparency.
不是吗
Right?
像你这样的富豪吗
Super-rich like you?
对
Yeah.
你希望任何人都能查看你的银行账户吗
Do you want everyone to see into your bank accounts?
我又没什么好隐瞒的
Well, I've got nothing to hide.
但外面某些人 有很多要隐瞒的
But there are people out there, with a lot to hide,
资流将会...
and River is gonna...
我们时间非常紧迫
We have very little time.
在他发布这个资流前 必须搞定这件事
This has got to be done before he releases this River thing.
我说的够清楚了吗
Do I make myself clear?
祝你生日快乐
'Happy birthday to you
加的斯  西班牙
祝你生日快乐
'Happy birthday to you
'Happy birthday
卡利托斯
'Carlitos!
祝你生日快乐
'Happy Birthday to you!'
生日快乐
要吹蜡烛吗 来试试 吹灭蜡烛 来 卡利托斯
Shall we do this? Let's have a go. Blow the candles out! Up, Carlito.
加油 卡利托斯
Come on, Carlito!
干得漂亮
Well done!
该拆礼物了
Presents!
礼物 礼物 礼物
Presents! Presents! Presents!
卡利托斯 这些都是给你的礼物
Carlito, all these presents for you!
-你要给他这个吗  -我其实 给你做了样东西 小家伙
- Do you want to give him this one? - I actually... I made you something, little one.
-真的吗  -对 在纽约时做的
- You did? - Yeah, in New York.
-你有时间做吗  -有
- Did you have time for this? - Yeah.
快看 快看
Look, look, look!
咱们要看看吗
Shall we have a look?
这是什么
What's this?
快看呐 卡利托斯
Look at this, Carlitos.
看呐
Look!
这个
This...
小家伙 这是一架美国飞机
...Little one, this is an American plane.
爸爸 别 不要
Daddy, no, don't...
你们记着不要发帖
Guys, no posting, you know.
妈妈
Mama?
好 好
OK, OK.
他们懂的
They know.
-我保证他们都懂  -抱歉 我知道你懂
- I promise, they know.  - Sorry, I know you know.
-你知道吗  -我知道
- You know.  - I know.
-怎么啦  -生日快乐
- What?  - Happy birthday.
敬畏上帝  尊敬国王  爱护兄弟情谊
贝尔法斯特  北爱尔兰
你还好吗 亲爱的
You alright, love?
一想到艾玛一个人在拘留室 我就受不了
I can't bear to think of Em all alone in a cell.
是啊
Aye...
还是在伦敦
...And over there in London.
如果她被关在这里 至少还能跟家人在一起
At least if they were holding her here, she'd be with her own people.
亲爱的
Love...
我们都经历过这些
We've both been through this.
他们第一次逮捕我的时候 我吓坏了
The first time they arrested me, they had me petrified.
但是你挺过来了
But you survived.
她跟我们不一样 她需要我们的陪伴
She's not like us, Larry. She needs us there.
我想过去找她
I wanna go over.
咱们哪有这么多钱
Where we gonna get the money for that?
-你可以跟诺曼要钱  -诺曼
- You could ask Norman?  - Norman?
诺曼有很多钱
Well, Norman has loads of money.
你跟他还有联系 不是吗
You're in touch with him, aren't ya?
-你知道他在哪吗  -我不能每次一有事
- Do you know where he is?  - I can't run to my wee brother
就去找我弟
every time we get in trouble.
这件事很严重 他们说她袭击了一名女警察
This is serious. They're saying she bottled a policewoman.
她需要我们
She needs us over there!
查尔斯
Charles.
嗨
Hi.
最近怎么样啊
还算过得去
No pain.
-有很多孩子哈  -总是有很多孩子
- A lot of children, eh?  - Always. Always children.
你没经历过这些吧
Different for you, no? You...
-你是独生子吗  -是的
- ...You only child?  - Yeah.
-抱歉  -没事
- Sorry. Sorry, um...  - No.
查尔斯 我的英语说的很不好
You know, Charlie, my... My English is very difficult.
你总是这么说 阿尔瓦罗 但你的英语很好
You always say that, Alvaro, but you speak very good English.
-得了吧  -真的
- Nah.  - No, it's...
-我才是根本学不会西班牙语 所以没关系  -不 你的西语说的不错
- Spanish is impossible for me, so it's all good...  - No! Your Spanish is better.
-真的吗  -是
- Really?  - Mm.
我从没跟你说过这些
You know, I never tell you.
但是每次你离开家
Always when you go away,
我就告诉大家
I tell everybody,
别担心 有我在这
don't worry. I here.
我会照顾好这个家 一切都没问题的
I look, everything is perfect, everything is OK.
所以 你有任何需要 随时跟我说
So... You need anything... Yeah.
-交给我吧  -你人真好 阿尔瓦罗
- I can do.  - That's very kind, Alvero,
我很感谢你 真的
and I appreciate it. Honestly.
查尔斯 有一件事
Look, Charlie. One thing.
-我有一个朋友  -好的
- I have a friend, OK?  - OK.
他有一间酒吧
And my friend has a... has a bar.
他想
And he offered to...
英语怎么说来着 想卖掉
How do you say... To, to sell, to sell. Yeah.
一部分 想卖掉半间
A part, half of the bar.
好的
OK.
如果你感兴趣
So, if you're interested,
我可以带你去见他
I can take you to my friend,
我们三个聊聊 看要不要买下来
and the three can speak, see if it's good.
听起来很不错 我很感兴趣
I think that would be... I think we should do that.
但是得等我
But I think maybe when I...
等我回来
...perhaps when I come back.
-回到这里吗  -是的
- Here?  - Yeah.
稍等我一下 就一会儿
Do you know what? Give me one, one second.
家人们
快过来 吃饭了
开曼大都会银行：您有一条新的安全消息 请登录您的在线账户查看
我得打个电话
I've just gotta make a quick call.
现在吗
是的 很快就好
Yeah, I gotta... Er, it will be quick.
不是吧
我马上回来
I'll be one minute.
快点啊
好的
Yeah.
查尔斯无时无刻不在工作
确实
但看看他努力工作换来的这一切
你找对人了
别废话了 快过来坐着吃
快点 虾都要凉了
你想做什么？
快速链接
账户
消息 （1条新消息）
付款
转账
14天前有375万欧元被存入我的账户，请求确认资金来源
关于 375 万欧元收款的回复：无法确认付款人身份
资金来自账户：DE89372400442532017000
慕尼黑 利奥波德街 慕尼黑PFB
慕尼黑
-不是吧 又来  -对不起
- No. Not again, please.  - I'm so sorry.
-服了  -是啊
- Oh, come on.  - I know.
这些人知道今天是他的生日 但他们就是这么不近人情
They know it's his birthday. They just have no empathy, these people.
-太抱歉了  -你昨天才刚回来
- I'm so sorry.  - You arrived only yesterday.
我知道
I know, I know I did.
各位 真是太抱歉了 我得走了
Guys, I'm so sorry, I'm gonna have to head off.
再见了 小家伙
Bye, bye little one. Bye, bye.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
我爱你 我很快就回来
I love you. I'll see you soon. I'll see you soon.
-再见  -我开车送你吧
- Ciao.  - OK, I'm driving you.
不用了 我叫了出租车
No, I booked a cab.
不准坐出租车
-你不能就这么离开  -不 我就要送你  -查尔斯
- You can't leave this.  - No, I'm driving you. - Charlie.
我还在这呢 放心
Hey, I here, OK?
好的 谢谢你 阿尔瓦罗
Yeah. Thanks, Alvaro.
再见
Bye, guys.
-再见  -再见  -再见
- Bye!Adios!  - Ciao!  - Bye!
-再见  -跟爸爸说再见
- Bye!  - Say bye, Daddy!
德国联邦情报局说 保安以为见到的是拉尔夫
The BND said the guard was convinced he was talking to the real Ralf.
说话的声音和语调一样 爱挖苦人
The voice, the intonation, the sarcasm.
很明显 他没有任何破绽
Apparently, everything was perfect.
这个人很擅长模仿
So our man is a mimic.
他擅长模仿 那他的语言能力肯定很强
And if he's a mimic, he's good with language,
所以他不一定是德国人
so he's not necessarily German.
放大背包给我看看
Er, enlarge the backpack for me?
防水帆布包
Waxed canvas.
很聪明地把商标去掉了
Of course he's taken the maker's tab off.
再放大 我看看商标位置
Enhance that so I can see where it was.
截几张图
Yeah. Grab some screenshots of that.
可以了 继续吗
Done. Shall I move on?
好的
Yeah.
他是右撇子
So he's righthanded...
停
Oh whoa, stop it there.
放大
Enlarge.
再放大
Keep going.
停停停
Whoa stop, stop, stop.
勃朗宁高威力三型手枪
Browning HiPower. Mark III.
明明可以选择威力更大的枪
Why would you go for a nine mil
为什么却要用九毫米手枪呢
when you could have something with a lot more stopping power?
你究竟有何意图
Why would you do that?
塞维利亚  西班牙
就这样吗
That's it?
你的心思又飘到工作上去了
You've gone to that place again.
-我的天啊  -我在这里
- Oh my God.  -I'm here.
我在这里呢
I'm here.
你爱我吗
爱
Yeah.
用西语说给我听
不要羞辱我
Don't humiliate me.
那用英语说吧
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
-你好  -你好吗
- Hola.  - How are you?
安达卢西亚大街 奥恩扎街的拐角处 谢谢
好的
OK.
英国护照  阿拉斯泰尔·瑟斯克
去圣胡斯塔火车站
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
你好 我是查尔斯
'Hi, this is Charles.'
有事请留言 我稍后回复
'Please leave a message and I'll get back to you.'
怎么了
什么怎么了
我还不清楚你这表情吗
妈 我没事
你到底说不说
妈 真没事 别烦我
告诉我吧
就是
我把查尔斯送到机场
之后我在花市看见他坐着出租车
真的吗
我尝试打他电话 但他手机关机了
什么
我早和你说过 你太容易相信别人了
是不是
你纵容他长期在外
他天天往外跑
你永远不知道他在哪 在做什么
查尔斯人很好
他爱我们 看他对卡利托斯就知道
发生什么事了
查尔斯在外面偷腥
什么
妈 我不是这么说的
要是那个外国人敢骗你 我就打断他的腿
冷静
我保证要杀了他
别激动
我只想解决问题
你开什么玩笑
该死
吃点东西吧 亲爱的
There you go, love.
拉里 联系诺曼吧
Larry, please. Call Norman.
我已经给他打过电话了
I've called him already.
打了两次
Twice.
如果他不回电 我会再打一次 好吗
If he doesn't call back soon, I'll try him again, OK?
商标是类似山脉形状的
The maker's tab was a sort of mountain range shape.
她
She...
你好 我在找一款背包
Hello, yes. I'm looking for a very specific backpack.
炭灰色 蜡布材质
Charcoal grey, wax canvas.
商标是山脉的形状
Mountain range maker's tab.
伊莎贝尔找你
Isabel's expecting you.
狙击手是英国人
The sniper's British.
别乱开玩笑
Don't even joke about that.
-并且他很可能在英国军队服役过  -你怎么知道
- And he's probably ex-British Army.  - You know that how?
即使受过军事训练 你的射击距离也只有他的一半
You need military training to make a shot at even half that distance.
那他服役的也不一定是英国军队
Doesn't necessarily mean he's one of ours.
他用勃朗宁高威力三型手枪 杀了埃利亚斯的保镖
He used a Browning HiPower Mark III to kill Elias's bodyguard
重伤了埃利亚斯
and to wound Elias.
这种手枪在2013年前是英国军队的标配
The HiPower was standard British Army issue until 2013.
很多部队都使用过该手枪
A lot of armed forces used the HiPower.
他的背包是由英国一家小型初创公司生产的
He had a backpack made by a small UK based startup
公司叫完美背包
called The Perfect Pack.
这种背包在八个月前上市
The backpack went on sale eight months ago.
只有两家零售商 位置都在利兹市
There are only two retailers, both in Leeds,
并且都不对境外售卖
and neither ships internationally.
也就是说 他曾在英国
That means he was here, in the UK.
也可能是他的同伙买给他的
Or an accomplice picked it up for him.
不 他是单独行动的
No. Our man works alone.
狙击手需要观察手
Snipers work with a spotter.
这次不一样 他独自射伤了埃利亚斯
Not this one. He was alone when he shot Elias
独自离开了公寓楼
and he was alone when he left the apartment building.
这么说 狙击手和造枪者都是英国人
So we think the sniper is British, and the gun maker is British.
-麻雀有消息了吗  -告诉她要怎么做了
- Have you heard from Sparrow?  - She knows what she has to do.
明早 她就会得知女儿死亡的消息
By tomorrow morning she'll know her daughter's dead,
你的筹码也就没了
and bang goes your leverage.
-给我多一点的时间  -不行
- I need more time.  - No.
我马上就要找到凶手了
I'm this close.
比安卡 我们已经如履薄冰了
Bianca... We're already on very thin ice.
建议你抓紧找麻雀要到消息
I suggest you encourage Sparrow to give you what you want.
在明早之前
By tomorrow.
喂 亲爱的
Hello, my love.
你什么时候回家
'What time are you gonna be home?'
不确定 希望不要太晚
Err, not sure. Not too late, I hope.
好的 我兄弟今晚要过来吃饭
'OK, OK. My brothers are coming at eight.'
我正在做穆萨卡
I'm cooking moussaka.
不过这道菜太难做了 他们最好喜欢吃
It's so complicated, though. They better love it.
他们会的 那晚上见
They will. Um, OK. I'll see you then.
-好的 别迟到了  -好的
- OK, don't be late.  - Yep. Alright.
-爱你  -拜拜
- Love you.  - Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
好
OK.
如果狙击手是退役军人
If our sniper was ex-Army,
并且他是伞兵团或皇家近卫师的成员
he would've done his sniper training
那么他会在皮尔布赖特基地接受狙击手训练
at Pirbright if he was a Para or Household Division.
如果他在其他部队服役
If he had another cap badge
那么他会去布雷肯的步兵战斗学校接受训练
he would've gone to the Infantry Battle School at Brecon.
让他们查询记录
We need them to go through their records.
找什么呢
And what are we looking for?
狙击高手
An exceptional candidate.
惯用右手 高个子 白人
Righthanded. Tall. White.
要让他们追溯多远的记录
And how far back do we want them to go?
假设狙击手五十岁以下
Assuming our man is under fifty...
大约查三十年的记录
I'd say about thirty years.
巴伐利亚  德国
哪位
Who is this?
我们在瑞典见过
'We met in Sweden.'
有什么我能帮你的
'How can I help' you?
我和我的同事商量过了 我们觉得应该做一笔交易
I have spoken to my colleagues, and we feel there's a deal to be done.
但我们需要面谈来确定细节
But we need to meet in person to work out the details.
我们不会再见面了
'We're not meeting again.'
这么大的交易 我们认为会面是必要的
For a deal of this size, we believe a meeting is essential.
我们必须在48小时内面谈
It has to be in person and it has to be in the next fortyeight hours.
好吧 但我恕难从命
Yeah, well, I'm afraid that's not happening.
我们已经预付了一百万美元来表达诚意
We've already shown you a million dollars of good faith.
如果我们在48小时内没有面谈 就找其他人了
If we can't meet in the next 48 hours, we'll have to move on.
喂
'Hello?'
你们来找我 我会给你提示
You'll have to come to me. 'I'll send instructions.'
等你消息
I look forward to it.
伦敦  英国
你好
Hi!
-你好  -刚好赶上
- Oh, hey. - Hi. Oh, just about on time.
看起来很棒
This looks great!
哇 好 很好
Oh wow, OK, OK. OK, OK.
丹魄红酒 配穆萨卡最合适
Er, Tempranillo, perfect for moussaka.
-还有白歌海娜 完美  -看吧 我有听你的话
Grenache blanc. This is perfect. Yeah, see, I do listen to you. Yeah.
或者是卖酒的人告诉她的
Or they told her at the wine shop.
哇 她等我的时候从没这么兴奋过
Oh wow. She's never that excited to see me.
-嘿  -你好
- Hey. - Hello.
-你好吗  -我不确定是哪一个
- You good? - I wasn't sure which one.
-绝对很棒  -爸爸
It's absolutely good. Dad.
肯定很棒 快来 进来 他来了
Absolutely fine. Come on, bring it in. There he is.
你还好吗 妈妈向你问好 见到你很高兴
You alright? Mum sends love. Good to see you, man.
-我很好 你好吗  -嗨
- I'm good, man. You alright? - Hi.
-见到你很高兴  -看起来不错
- Good to see you. - Looking good, looking good.
-你好吗  -嗨
- You good? - Hi!
-你好吗  -我很好 你呢  -也好
- How are you? - I'm good, you? - Yeah.
我想要一杯百加得加可乐
I wanted a Bacardi and coke.
-你刚才要的是杜松子酒  -我要的是百加得
You asked for a gin. I asked for a Bacardi.
顺便买包薯片
And get a pack of crisps while you're at it.
噢
Aye.
第二次总该买对了吧
Second time lucky.
伏特加 加可乐
Vodka and coke.
杜松子酒加可乐
Gin and coke?
你一点都不幽默 拉里
You're not funny, Larry.
你们喜欢吗
Do you like it?
你知道奥利匹斯山上的众神嘛
You see the gods on Mount Olympus, yeah,
他们经常吃一种东西叫仙果
they used to eat this thing called ambrosia.
但后来贾思敏送了一些她最拿手的穆萨卡
But then Jasmine goes and sends them up some of her famous moussaka.
-你知道众神怎么说  -不知道
- You know what they said? - No.
不知道吗
You don't know what they said?
他们说 去他妈的仙果
They said, Fuck ambrosia.
-从今往后 他们只吃贾思敏的穆萨卡  -上帝啊
- Because from now on its Jasmine's - moussaka. - Oh, god.
他在说什么呢
What is he talking about?
这是对你的赞美
It's a brainy compliment.
-看得出来 你没有把古典文学忘干净啊 亚当  -别这样
- I can see that the classics aren't wasted on you, Adam. - Come on.
失陪一下
One second.
再来点不
Uh... top up?
麻雀  短信
指挥中心
请说出您的电话验证码的第2位 第3位和第6位
'Please give characters two, three and six of your telephone ID.'
0 1 9
Zero, one, nine.
有什么可以帮您
'How I can help?'
我急需定位一部手机
I need a priority location on a phone.
-作为一个曾经的小伙子  -那是很多年前了
- Speaking as a former teenage boy...  - A very long time ago.
-这就是我们的工作 把事情搞砸  -没错
- That's what we do. We fuck it up. - That is true.
事实如此 确实
It's facts. It's facts.
-真要走吗  -抱歉
- Seriously? - I'm sorry.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉 贾思敏
I'm sorry, Jas.
回头见 各位
Um, I'll see you soon, boys.
到家给我们打电话 好吗
Call us when you get there, yeah?
我尽量
I'll try.
慕尼黑  德国
詹森女士 这是留给您的
Ms Jansone? This has been left for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
英国花园  10:00  不要带手机
诺曼还在白俄罗斯
Norman's still at the location in Belarus.
我有麻雀打来的九个未接电话
I have nine missed calls from Sparrow.
她知道艾玛的事了吗
Does she know about Emma?
里加  拉脱维亚
还不知道
'Not yet.
但很快就有人告诉他了
But at some point soon she's going to have to be told.'
如果麻雀发现了 她会告诉拉里 拉里会告诉他哥
If Sparrow finds out, she'll tell Larry, who will tell his brother.
我看看能做什么
'I'll see what I can do.'
斯宾塞在入境处等你 他会带你穿过边境
Spencer's waiting in arrivals. He'll get you across the border.
你确保抓住诺曼就行
Just make sure you get Norman.
-全靠你了  -好
- 'We're counting on you.' - Yeah.
-斯宾塞  -对
- Spencer? - Yeah.
这边
This way.
拉脱维亚人知道我们在他们的底盘上行动
The Latvians know we're operating on their turf.
他们睁只眼闭只眼 但是白俄罗斯人不可能这样
They're friendly, but Belarus is very hostile.
我们必须尽快抓住目标
We need to get to the target as soon as possible.
到斯马尔霍尼要开6小时 托比是我们的司机
The journey to Smarhon's six hours. Toby's our wheels.
科林会协助我们进行抓捕
Colin'll be with us for the grab.
出发
Let's go.
欢迎来到里加
继续直视前方
You can keep looking straight ahead.
你把电话留在酒店了吗
Have you left your phone at the hotel?
当然
Of course.
很好
Good.
我的客户需要知道 从专业角度来看
My clients need to know if you think it's possible,
这事可行吗
speaking as a professional?
乌达查可能觉得自己是神 但不意味着他是不朽的
Well, er, UDC may think he's God, but that doesn't mean he's immortal.
在费用问题上 我们还有一些分歧
We're still some way apart on the fee.
也许我们可以各退一步
Perhaps we can meet in the middle?
我们不是恐怖分子
We're not terrorists, you know.
我们是爱国者 我们在捍卫自己的生活方式
We're patriots. We're defending our way of life.
我对你们想杀他的理由毫无兴趣
I have fuck all interest in why you want him dead.
一亿不是小数目
A hundred million is a big ask.
你们付钱让我杀他
You're paying me to kill him.
我收的钱与承担的风险是成正比的
I am charging you for getting away.
从专业角度来看
And, speaking as a professional,
风险评估很重要
getting away is an important consideration.
预付一半 事成后付清另一半
It's half in advance, half on delivery.
不行 定金不会少
No. Half up front won't fly, but
但我已获准向你提供两千万的行动费用
I am authorised to pay you a commencement fee of twenty million dollars.
我今天就可以安排
I could do that today.
你觉得可以接受吗
Would that be acceptable?
好吧
Yeah.
任务必须在28号之前完成
The job has to be completed by the 28th.
我不喜欢匆匆忙忙
I'm not in the habit of being hurried.
乌达查计划在28号发布资流 没得商量
UDC releases River on the 28th. It's nonnegotiable.
你做得到吗
Can you do it?
钱到账后 我就开始行动
Once the payment is in my bank account, I will get to work.
为什么你还在慕尼黑
Why are you still in Munich?
你杀死曼弗雷德·菲斯特已经快一周了
It's been nearly a week since you killed Manfred Fest.
有什么遗留问题
Have you loose ends to tie up?
我们不希望你做任何吸引眼球的事情
We don't want you doing anything that attracts attention or
也不希望你做任何与工作无关的危险事情
that puts you in jeopardy that's not in service of the job.
没有遗留问题
There are no loose ends.
很好
Good.
那就这么定了
Then we have a deal.
定了
We have a deal.
继续直视前方
Keep looking straight ahead.
以后联络时
In future communications...
我们使用罗丹作为目标代号
...we'll use the code name Rodin for the target.
罗丹
Rodin.
很好
Very good.
你也需要一个代号
And we'll need a code name for you, too.
豺狼怎么样
Why not the Jackal?
为什么不呢
Why not?
对 瑟斯克先生在我这
好
两周前 瑟斯克先生账户进了一大笔钱
他没想到会收到这笔钱
转账是通过我们银行完成的
账号是
DE
对
对 瑟斯克先生正在核实
知道了
好 谢谢
先生 非常感谢您的耐心等待
Sir, thank you so much for your patience.
瑟斯克先生 这笔钱是从公司账户支付的
Mr. Thirsk. So that payment was made from a company account.
赫勒莉妮
HelleLinie. Well,
关于赫勒莉妮 你能告诉我什么
what can you tell me about HelleLinie?
恐怕我们不能透露这些信息
I'm afraid we're not authorised to give out that information,
但可以在网上查到公司的注册信息
but the national company register is available online.
还有别的事情我可以帮您吗
Is there anything else I can help you with?
没有 谢谢
Er, no, thank you.
搜索
赫勒莉妮有限责任公司
注册地：菲尔特地区法院
注册编号：HRB 3868
母公司：特林有限责任公司（注册地：荷兰）
荷兰商会
搜索注册信息
特林有限责任公司
结果（共1条）
注册编号：73614661
合伙企业
母公司：杜波依斯有限责任公司（注册地：法国）
地点编号： 000041632362
（注册地：法国）
法兰西共和国
公司法律信息官方查询网站
你的搜索
杜波依斯有限责任公司
结果 (1)
母公司：纽顿有限公司  (注册地：英国)
"纽顿有限公司"  (注册地：英国)
英国政府网站
查找及更新公司信息
查询登记册
输入公司名称、编号或管理人员姓名
纽顿有限公司
找到1条结果
公司编号 01999756
母公司：阿奇福特信托基金（私人公司）
注册地：根西岛
公司编号 01999756
母公司：阿奇福特信托基金（私人公司）
注册地：根西岛
二十分钟后到达边境
Twenty minutes to the border.
目的地：斯马尔霍尼   52分钟 · 42.9英里 · 预计到达时间16:15
诺曼还在原地
Norman hasn't moved.
非法行为和不道德行为记录
阿奇福特信托基金 根西岛
找到1条结果
阿奇福特信托基金
根西私人信托数据库
名称　　　　　　阿奇福特信托基金
司法管辖区　　　未知
注册号　　　　　05086764
成立日期　　　　2004年3月29日
国家　　　　　　根西岛（海峡群岛）
解散日期　　　　2004年10月8日
职位
组织
阿奇福特信托基金
汉斯·兰格
董事
董事职位　❷
阿奇福特信托基金
奥帕潘有限责任公司
董事
斯马尔霍尼  白俄罗斯
距房屋四十米 移动中
40 meters out at the rear. Moving.
移动中
Moving.
距房屋二十五米 移动中
25 meters out at the rear. Moving.
移动中
Moving.
接近前门 移动中
'Approaching front door. Moving.'
移动中
Moving.
距房屋十米 移动中
10 meters out at the rear. Moving.
各就各位了吗
Everyone in position?
两人就位
Two in position.
诺曼 屋子被包围了
Norman! The house is surrounded!
放下武器 出来投降
Throw your weapons down and come outside!
我数三
On my count.
三 二 一 上膛
Three, two, one... breech!
有人受伤
Man down!
操
Fuck.
两人受伤 目标正徒步逃走
We're two down. Target escaping on foot.
追击中
In pursuit.
操
Fuck!
B队呼叫T队 我们中埋伏了 他知道我们要来
Bravo to Tango. We were set up. He knew we were coming.
两人受伤 立即从指定地点撤离
Two pax down. Immediate extraction from X=Ray now.
三十秒后到达
'30 seconds out.'
最新  奥帕潘公司年度庆祝晚会
当奥帕潘-克雷多慈善晚宴落下帷幕 我们不禁思考 正是因为大家的慷慨和爱心 才让这一切成为可能
现场充满了强烈的使命感 个人 企业和社区共同努力 一起推动积极的改变
埃利亚斯·费斯特与汉斯·兰格
埃利亚斯·费斯特
去你妈的
Fuck. You.